Register of the Ghanaian Subject Collection, 1945-2001.
Hoover Institution Archives
Ghanaian Subject Collection,
1945-2001
XX782
4 manuscript boxes, 1 oversize box (2.3 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Electronic bulletins, pamphlets, reports, communiqués, serial issues, clippings, and other printed matter, relating to political, social and economic conditions in Ghana.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Materials were acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Ghana.; Africa.
Series Description
- SUBJECT FILE, 1951-1994. (Boxes 1-2)
  Brochures, bulletins, clippings, communiques, election guide, handbook, flyers, membership forms, pamphlets, printed matter, research papers, speeches, statements and working papers relating to the economic, social, political and religious conditions in Ghana
- OVERSIZE MATERIAL, 1981-1992. (Box 3)
  Calendar, election posters, issues of newspapers and a plastic bag relating to years of revolutionary progress, election and the candidates from the different political parties and to various scenes from Ghanaian life
Container List
See card catalog for increments that may have been received after December 1994
- SUBJECT FILE, 1951-1994
  - General (Box 1)
  - Agriculture
  - Culture
  - Economics
  - Education
  - Elections
    - 1987
    - 1992
  - Health
  - Justice and judicial system
  - Politics and government
  - Religion (Box 2)
  - Trade Union Congress. Includes printed copy of its constitution
- OVERSIZE MATERIAL, 1981-1992
  - Election posters with pictures of candidates belonging to various parties, n.d. (Box 3)
  - Calendar depicting various scenes from Ghanaian life, 1991-1992
  - Plastic bag with a picture of the Ghanaian flag and dates indicating "A Decade of Revolutionary Progress"
  - The Patriot
    - Undated
    - 1992
      - August
      - September-October
- Incremental Materials (Box 4:)
  Thsi addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archvies know if you would like to see this material described.